[{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678961573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":22847,"timeElapsed":150860},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678976364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":14787,"timeElapsed":165651},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678984041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":7672,"timeElapsed":173328},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678989887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":5841,"timeElapsed":179175},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678994878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4985,"timeElapsed":184165},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679025030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":30147,"timeElapsed":214317},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679036616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":11582,"timeElapsed":225904},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":29417,"timeElapsed":255323},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679076465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":10427,"timeElapsed":265753},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":12347,"timeElapsed":283364},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":9121,"timeElapsed":292490},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679108592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5388,"timeElapsed":297880},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679114172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5577,"timeElapsed":303460},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679117924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3749,"timeElapsed":307212},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679128163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":10236,"timeElapsed":317451},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679136282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8114,"timeElapsed":325569},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679147567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11283,"timeElapsed":336855},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679162899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":15329,"timeElapsed":352187},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679178479,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":15573,"timeElapsed":367767},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679186981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6584,"timeElapsed":376269},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679191693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4710,"timeElapsed":380981},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679195675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3979,"timeElapsed":384963},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679200669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4992,"timeElapsed":389957},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679204829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4155,"timeElapsed":394116},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679226895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":22060,"timeElapsed":416183},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679231660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4760,"timeElapsed":420948},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679235977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4310,"timeElapsed":425265},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679241303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":5320,"timeElapsed":430591},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679253177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":10046,"timeElapsed":442465},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679265903,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":12722,"timeElapsed":455191},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679270384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4479,"timeElapsed":459672},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679274143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3756,"timeElapsed":463431},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679280277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6128,"timeElapsed":469564},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679287698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7414,"timeElapsed":476986},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679291578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3877,"timeElapsed":480866},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679297927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6346,"timeElapsed":487215},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679303415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5485,"timeElapsed":492703},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679316630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":11311,"timeElapsed":505918},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679323967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7334,"timeElapsed":513254},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679327730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3760,"timeElapsed":517018},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679331214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3483,"timeElapsed":520502},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679334578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3362,"timeElapsed":523866},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679358128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":23548,"timeElapsed":547416},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679369409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":11278,"timeElapsed":558697},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679382479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":13066,"timeElapsed":571767},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679391110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":8627,"timeElapsed":580398},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679412007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":19018,"timeElapsed":601295},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679418664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6652,"timeElapsed":607951},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679421883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3214,"timeElapsed":611171},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679425252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3367,"timeElapsed":614540},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679429646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4392,"timeElapsed":618934},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679441005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":11357,"timeElapsed":630293},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679459170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":18162,"timeElapsed":648458},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679479052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":19879,"timeElapsed":668340},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679485102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":6048,"timeElapsed":674390},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679499514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":12936,"timeElapsed":688802},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679502997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3480,"timeElapsed":692285},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679507034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4034,"timeElapsed":696322},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679510821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3784,"timeElapsed":700109},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679514180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3358,"timeElapsed":703468},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679518999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4816,"timeElapsed":708287},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679523720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4720,"timeElapsed":713008},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679527863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4140,"timeElapsed":717151},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679534194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6328,"timeElapsed":723482},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679554993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":18787,"timeElapsed":744281},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679558980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3983,"timeElapsed":748268},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679563728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4743,"timeElapsed":753016},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679567745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4012,"timeElapsed":757032},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679581555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":13807,"timeElapsed":770843},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679593810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":12252,"timeElapsed":783098},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679600573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6759,"timeElapsed":789861},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679604714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4139,"timeElapsed":794002},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679615230,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10513,"timeElapsed":804517},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679622223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":6988,"timeElapsed":811511},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679636528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12169,"timeElapsed":825816},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679640171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3639,"timeElapsed":829459},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679643669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3496,"timeElapsed":832957},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679647819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4147,"timeElapsed":837107},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679652259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4437,"timeElapsed":841547},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679656536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4272,"timeElapsed":845824},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679660358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3819,"timeElapsed":849646},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679668862,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8502,"timeElapsed":858150},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679672474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3608,"timeElapsed":861762},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679680237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":6043,"timeElapsed":869525},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679683538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3298,"timeElapsed":872826},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679687099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3558,"timeElapsed":876387},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679690687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3581,"timeElapsed":879975},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679693897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3206,"timeElapsed":883185},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679707251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":13350,"timeElapsed":896538},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679711265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4009,"timeElapsed":900553},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679717673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6404,"timeElapsed":906961},{"subjectID":"vnvmkjbmdh","prolificID":"67292f5b77e0c806cf844b00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3f4f06b14a3166647c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679737433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":19755,"timeElapsed":926721}]